<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peter Teixeira</title>
    <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Peter Teixeira</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 16:12:21 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Avatar: The Legend of Korra (A TV Reflection)</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/legend-of-korra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 16:12:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/legend-of-korra/</guid>
      <description>Avatar: Legend of Korra is best known for not being Avatar: The Last Airbender. It received a certain amount of hate when it came out, and has long been viewed as greatly overshadowed by its predecessor. That view is both accurate and somewhat unfair. Legend of Korra is a very different show than The Last Airbender, with different conflicts and a dramatically different view of trauma, especially emotional trauma, than its predecessor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Design</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/on-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 20:12:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/on-design/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been thinking about this for a while, and figured I’d put it down someplace. It starts out kinda technical, but I promise it’s actually a metaphor for something 1.
In Linux there’s a particular syscall (fork) that lets you start a new process from a running process. It’s something that gets used all the time, and there’s nothing inherently weird about it. You call it, it starts a new process, and gives you back the ID of the new process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Owl House Season One (A TV Reflection)</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/the-owl-house-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 16:56:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/the-owl-house-s1/</guid>
      <description>Luz’s relationship with her mother isn’t explored very much in the show, even though it’s such a central part of her motivations. The season ends with her voice memo to Camilla, and specifically with Luz telling her mother that she loves her. But Luz’s love for her mother is also deeply shadowed by her that she will disappoint her mother, or that she already has. “Enchanting Grom Fright” very clearly shows how Luz reacts to her mother’s consternation that she’s not at camp, that she’s holding a weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Render Coffee</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/render-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 11:44:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/render-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Info 563 Columbus Ave,Boston, MA 02118
Hours: 8a-4p weekends, 7a-2p weekdays
https://rendercoffeebar.com
(There&amp;rsquo;s also a second location in the Financial district, but I&amp;rsquo;ve never been there)
Review Render Coffee&amp;rsquo;s orders work a little differently than at other places I&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed in the past, so this review might be graded a little unfairly relative to others. You can&amp;rsquo;t really just order an egg sammy - for one thing, the eggs are baked rather than fried or scrambled and for another you get a vegetable (or a meat, I guess) on your sandwich for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 19:11:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/about/</guid>
      <description>About this Blog I sincerely intended this to be a tech blog. It turns out, I barely have tech-ish ideas at work, and having them outside of work seems a lot like &amp;hellip; work. So I&amp;rsquo;m not doing that. Which isn&amp;rsquo;t to say that I&amp;rsquo;m definitely not put tech-related ideas on here, but I&amp;rsquo;m definitely not going to make myself do that.
If you do want tech-adjacent posts in domains that I&amp;rsquo;m interested in, why don&amp;rsquo;t you check out Jess Frazelle&amp;rsquo;s blog or Rachel Kroll&amp;rsquo;s or Dan Luu&amp;rsquo;s, or Cindy Sridharan&amp;rsquo;s (on Medium, unfortunately)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She-Ra and the Princesses of Power (A TV Reflection)</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/she-ra-and-the-princesses-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 20:39:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/she-ra-and-the-princesses-of-power/</guid>
      <description>Author&amp;rsquo;s Note: This was the first piece of long-form writing I&amp;rsquo;ve done in about two years, and the first piece of writing about literature that I&amp;rsquo;ve done in about seven years. It reads like a mediocre high-school essay, because it basically is. I&amp;rsquo;ve written several pieces since, which I like to think read a little nicer than this. I will certainly re-watch She-Ra, probably in the near future, and when I do that I&amp;rsquo;ll come back to this post and re-write it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farmer&#39;s Horse</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/farmers-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 22:37:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/farmers-horse/</guid>
      <description>Info 374 Mass Ave, Boston MA
Hours: 8-3 weekdays, with slightly different hours weekends.
Review Farmer&amp;rsquo;s Horse has been something of a lifesaver for me in quarantine. It&amp;rsquo;s about two blocks from where I live (which is great, given that I am permanently WFH now) and has been open through quarantine. If that were the end of the story, I&amp;rsquo;d be more than happy to support them. Sitting at home doing work has, quite frankly, been pretty bad for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haute Coffee</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/haute-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 12:34:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/haute-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Haute Coffee Info 1 Canal Park,Cambridge MA
Hours: 7-4, closed Sundays.
https://myhautecoffee.com/
Review Now for the coffee show that I work right next to. Egg sandwiches are served on brioche and are pretty good. Served hot, with good eggs and good cheese. There&amp;rsquo;s only one, small problem - the sandwhich is somewhat small. The brioche, while tasty, is about the size of a dinner role and there&amp;rsquo;s one egg. You can add vegetables or meat, which is probably the most reasonable thing to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pavement Coffeehouse</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/pavement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 21:34:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/pavement/</guid>
      <description>Pavement Coffeehouse Info 44 Gainsborough St,Boston MA 02115
Hours: Generally speaking 7-7, with some varience for holiday and summer hours
https://pavementcoffeehouse.com/
Review I live literally around the block from the Symphony Pavement location and am not a big fan of cooking weekend mornings, so I&amp;rsquo;ve been to Pavement an unfortunate number of times. It really does have a lot to recommend it - the coffee (and other drinks, like the matcha latte) are good, if expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uses</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/uses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:27:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/uses/</guid>
      <description>Tools I Use (Inspired by awesome-uses)
Development Environment  Visual Studio Code (or Intellij, or Vim. But mostly VSCode)  A side note about Vim - I&amp;rsquo;m comfortable with it, but (no longer) evangelical about it. It&amp;rsquo;s an editor, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, and I now know it well enough that it stays out of my way. I&amp;rsquo;m sure if I bothered to configure nano, I&amp;rsquo;d feel the same about that.   Konsole Zsh (+ antibody to manage plugins) I currently use PopOS with the default (Gnome-derived) theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
