<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peter Teixeira</title>
    <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Peter Teixeira</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 20:39:01 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>She-Ra and the Princesses of Power (A TV Reflection)</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/she-ra-and-the-princesses-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 20:39:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/she-ra-and-the-princesses-of-power/</guid>
      <description>She-Ra and the Princesses of Power isn’t terribly subtle in its moralizing. At one point in S5E12 Princess Entrapta tells Hordak that it&amp;rsquo;s his differences from his hive-mind brothers that make him special. It also doesn’t need to be. She-Ra is grounded on how well the characters are developed and humanized, from the four-legged non-verbal robot Emily to the Best Friends Squad at the center of the show to the villains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haute Coffee</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/haute-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 12:34:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/haute-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Haute Coffee Info 1 Canal Park,
Cambridge MA
Hours: 7-4, closed Sundays.
https://myhautecoffee.com/
Review Now for the coffee show that I work right next to. Egg sandwiches are served on brioche and are pretty good. Served hot, with good eggs and good cheese. There&amp;rsquo;s only one, small problem - the sandwhich is somewhat small. The brioche, while tasty, is about the size of a dinner role and there&amp;rsquo;s one egg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pavement Coffeehouse</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/pavement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 21:34:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/pavement/</guid>
      <description>Pavement Coffeehouse Info 44 Gainsborough St,
Boston MA 02115
Hours: Generally speaking 7-7, with some varience for holiday and summer hours
https://pavementcoffeehouse.com/
Review I live literally around the block from the Symphony Pavement location and am not a big fan of cooking weekend mornings, so I&amp;rsquo;ve been to Pavement an unfortunate number of times. It really does have a lot to recommend it - the coffee (and other drinks, like the matcha latte) are good, if expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uses</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/uses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:27:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/uses/</guid>
      <description>Tools I Use (Inspired by awesome-uses)
Development Environment  Visual Studio Code (or Intellij, or Vim. But mostly VSCode)  A side note about Vim - I&amp;rsquo;m comfortable with it, but (no longer) evangelical about it. It&amp;rsquo;s an editor, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, and I now know it well enough that it stays out of my way. I&amp;rsquo;m sure if I bothered to configure nano, I&amp;rsquo;d feel the same about that.  Konsole Zsh (+ antibody to manage plugins) I currently use PopOS with the default (Gnome-derived) theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>