<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>television on Peter Teixeira</title>
    <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/tags/television/</link>
    <description>Recent content in television on Peter Teixeira</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 16:12:21 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/tags/television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Avatar: The Legend of Korra (A TV Reflection)</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/legend-of-korra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 16:12:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/legend-of-korra/</guid>
      <description>Avatar: Legend of Korra is best known for not being Avatar: The Last Airbender. It received a certain amount of hate when it came out, and has long been viewed as greatly overshadowed by its predecessor. That view is both accurate and somewhat unfair. Legend of Korra is a very different show than The Last Airbender, with different conflicts and a dramatically different view of trauma, especially emotional trauma, than its predecessor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Owl House Season One (A TV Reflection)</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/the-owl-house-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 16:56:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/the-owl-house-s1/</guid>
      <description>Luz’s relationship with her mother isn’t explored very much in the show, even though it’s such a central part of her motivations. The season ends with her voice memo to Camilla, and specifically with Luz telling her mother that she loves her. But Luz’s love for her mother is also deeply shadowed by her that she will disappoint her mother, or that she already has. “Enchanting Grom Fright” very clearly shows how Luz reacts to her mother’s consternation that she’s not at camp, that she’s holding a weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She-Ra and the Princesses of Power (A TV Reflection)</title>
      <link>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/she-ra-and-the-princesses-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 20:39:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptrteixeira.github.io/me/posts/she-ra-and-the-princesses-of-power/</guid>
      <description>Author&amp;rsquo;s Note: This was the first piece of long-form writing I&amp;rsquo;ve done in about two years, and the first piece of writing about literature that I&amp;rsquo;ve done in about seven years. It reads like a mediocre high-school essay, because it basically is. I&amp;rsquo;ve written several pieces since, which I like to think read a little nicer than this. I will certainly re-watch She-Ra, probably in the near future, and when I do that I&amp;rsquo;ll come back to this post and re-write it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
